<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DubaiTravel</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!--Description of Burj Khalifa-->
    <string name="desc_burj_khalifa">The Burj Khalifa,
        is a skyscraper in Dubai, U.A.E.
        With a total height of 829.8 m,
        the Burj Khalifa is currently the tallest structure in the world.</string>
    <string name="loc_burj_khalifa">Location : Downtown Dubai</string>

    <!--Description of Burj Al Arab-->
    <string name="desc_burj_al_arab">The Burj al-Arab is a 7 star luxury hotel located in Dubai,
        U.A.E. It is the third tallest hotel in the world.</string>

    <!--Description of Atlantis-->
    <string name="desc_atlantis">Atlantis, The Palm is a UAE luxury hotel resort located at the apex
        of the Palm Jumeirah in the United Arab Emirates.</string>

    <!--Description of Wild Wadi-->
    <string name="desc_wild_wadi">The Wild Wadi Water Park is an outdoor water park in Dubai, U.A.E.
        Situated in the area of Jumeirah, next to the Burj Al Arab.</string>

    <string name="desc_restaurant_one">Coya: Coya not only serves the best food in the city, but some of the best dishes
        we\'ve eaten anywhere. Ever. It\'s popular and has been since it opened.  </string>

    <string name="desc_restaurant_two">Play: A restaurant that opened with an air of exclusivity, this new
        "Mediterrasian" eatery takes the two cuisines and puts together dishes to stunning effect.</string>

    <string name="desc_restaurant_three">Pai Thai: Yes, it has been around a while, and yes, it\'s popular with
        tourists. But it\'s also absolutely fantastic.</string>

    <string name="desc_restaurant_four">Nusr-Et: Serving Turkish classics and some of the best cuts of meats
        in town, Nusr-Et has done wonders since it opened, managing to combine fine dining with a
        no-nonsense approach.</string>

    <string name="desc_mall_one">Mall of the Emirates: MOE is the ultimate destination for leisure,
        entertainment, and shopping. It is also the world’s first shopping resort with dual five star
        hotels.</string>

    <string name="desc_mall_two">Ibn Battuta: Ibn Battuta was a 14th Century Arab scholar who travelled 120,000 km
        over 30 years. This mall, inspired by him, gives us an insight into the places he has visited.
        Who wouldn\’t love a bit of medieval scenery while shopping?</string>

    <string name="desc_mall_three">Deira City Centre: It may not be the shiniest and it is definitely not the biggest,
        but Deira City Centre has always been one of the favourite shopping destinations for the
        residents of old Dubai.</string>

    <string name="desc_mall_four">Dubai Mall: Now it\'s time for the most elaborate mall of them all, although
        the one with the least elaborate name: The Dubai Mall. It\’s the largest in the world and there
        is barely a brand or outlet that isn\’t set up here.</string>

    <string name="desc_off_one">Ras Al Khor Wildlife Sanctuary: This large salt water lagoon is only
        10 minutes drive from World Trade Centre and you can see large numbers of migratory wild birds
        including flamingoes and eagles from the hides.</string>

    <string name="desc_off_two">MAKE Business Hub: An urban cafe that promotes entrepreneurs and aims
        to foster creativity with free-to-use facilities, workshops and seminars. A good place to go
        if you are in Dubai for business or want to network.</string>

    <string name="desc_off_three">Bastakiya: The Emirati breakfasts and lunches at the Cultural Centre
        in Bastakiya go down well with my guests. The food is cooked and served by locals who will chat
        to you about life in UAE.</string>

    <string name="desc_off_four">Pavilion Downtown: They have art exhibitions, a library, cafe and
        cinema showing local and international films.</string>
</resources>
